mathgametime.com 2014-11-22

# Privacy Policy – Math Game Time

MathGameTime.com Privacy Policy. Effective as of April 5, 2011. At  
MathGameTime.com, a website operated by Fila, LLC, we are committed to  
respecting people’s privacy online. We are also committed to providing you  
with the very best experience we can on our website. In order to do so, we  
may gather certain personal information about you. Please read the following  
policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you  
make full use of our website. By using MathGameTime.com, you consent to the  
collection and use of your information by Fila LLC as described in this  
Policy, and you signify your agreement to the MathGameTime Privacy Policy.  
Information submitted by you for inclusion on MathGameTime.com.

Please remember that if you post any of your personal information in public  
areas of MathGameTime.com, such as in online forums or chat rooms, such  
information may be collected and used by others over whom we have no  
control. We are not responsible for the use made by third parties of  
information you post or otherwise make available in public areas of  
MathGameTime.com. MathGameTime.com members can invite friends to join  
MathGameTime.com by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation  
system. Fila LLC stores the email addresses that you provide so that the  
respondents may be added to your network, and also to send reminders of the  
invitations. When you visit MathGameTime.com, we collect some basic  
information that does not identify individual users. This includes which  
pages are visited and any feedback from our visitors. We then aggregate this  
information with other pieces of information to improve our site and make  
your experience on the site as valuable and efficient as possible.

When you register with MathGameTime.com, we collect personal information  
such as name, age, address, phone and email in order to set up your account.  
In addition to the information we collect upon your initial registration  
with MathGameTime.com, we may ask you for personal information at other  
times, including, but not limited to, when you enter promotions or contests,  
and when you respond to a survey. Upon canceling your MathGameTime.com  
account, you have the right to request deletion of your account information,  
subject to our need to keep appropriate archives for our business  
operations. What do we do with the information we collect? 1. It is used to  
set up and maintain your MathGameTime.com account. If you provide us with  
your mobile phone information, we may use such information to communicate  
with you regarding MathGameTime.com by SMS, MMS, text message or other  
electronic means to a mobile device. 2. Your phone number may be used in the  
event that our customer service representatives need to contact you and  
cannot reach you by email. 4. Credit card information is used to bill you  
for products you have ordered and to track sales. 5. Your personal  
information will never be sold to any other website owner or merchant. We  
hate junk mail as much as you. This is why we will only send you email about  
items that we feel you should know about. This includes special promotional  
items, membership changes, terms and conditions changes, Holiday cards, and  
the latest happenings on MathGameTime.com.

When we send you emails that include a link to the MathGameTime.com site,  
that link may contain an alphanumeric identifier that allows us to identify  
the person to whom we sent the message so that we can personalize our  
content for that individual. Email Opt-out Users who no longer wish to  
receive our email updates or other notifications may opt-out of receiving  
these communications by following the instructions contained in the  
applicable email or by logging-in and changing their account settings.  
Credit Card Processing Credit card transactions are handled by a third-party  
processor that receives credit card numbers and other personally identifying  
information only to verify credit card accounts and process transactions.  
Credit card security is an important aspect of the online experience. We  
ensure that our processor use encryption technology to keep your credit card  
information safe. To ensure that your information is even more secure, if we  
ever collect your credit card information, it will be stored for the  
duration of the transaction on a server that isn't accessible from the  
Internet. With whom do we share your information and for what purpose? Fila  
LLC does not sell, rent, or trade any personally identifying information  
with others. However, when one or more of our business partners co-sponsor a  
service, promotion and/or contest, we may share some or all of the  
information collected in connection with such service, promotion or contest  
with the co-sponsor(s). If we intend to share such information, you will be  
notified prior to the collection of that information. If you do not want  
your information to be shared, you will be able to choose not to allow the  
transfer by not using or signing up for that particular service, promotion  
or contest.

We may also aggregate user information in a non-personally identifiable  
manner with advertisers and other third parties in order to present to users  
more targeted advertising, products and services. We may contract with third  
parties to conduct research and marketing on our behalf. Such third parties  
will be fully bound by an obligation of confidentiality to Fila LLC and may  
not use any personally-identifiable information provided by us other than as  
expressly instructed by us and in strict compliance with the terms of this  
Privacy Policy. Some entities that have links on our site may collect  
personally identifying information about you when you access or utilize  
those links. Fila LLC does not control the collection or use of such  
information, and the practices of those advertisers and websites are not  
covered by this Privacy Policy. It is important to note that these entities  
may not follow the same privacy policies as Fila LLC. For instance, if you  
click on an advertisement on MathGameTime.com, you may be taken away from  
MathGameTime.com to an entirely different site. These links can also be from  
advertisers, content providers and/or partners who may use Math Game Time’s  
logo and/or style as a result of a co-branding agreement yet they may still  
not follow the same privacy policies as Math Game Time.

What are “cookies” and “web beacons” and how do we use them? Our site may  
use “cookies” and “web beacons” to speed navigation, keep track of items,  
and provide you with custom-tailored services. A “web beacon” is an embedded  
GIF file that specifically helps us track whether you have viewed a specific  
piece of content. We also use “cookies” to remember information you gave us  
so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit the site. By showing us  
how and when visitors use the site, “cookies” and “web beacons” help us see  
which site areas and content are popular and which are not. We also collect  
IP addresses for system administration and to report aggregate information  
to any sponsors. Some advertisers or websites that have links on our site  
may also use their own “cookies.” Most browsers are initially set to accept  
“cookies.” If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse “cookies.” You will  
not be able to use our service if you turn off the “cookies” option.  
Security for MathGameTime.com member accounts are secured by member-created  
passwords. In addition, we use reasonable measures to protect member  
information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to  
member information to those employees who need access to perform their job  
functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff.  
However, please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account  
information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and  
other factors may compromise the security of our member information at any  
time. Business transitions In the event Math Game Time goes through a  
business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or  
sale of a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most  
instances, be part of the assets transferred.

Users Located Outside of the United States - We make an effort to protect  
the personal information of all users of MathGameTime.com. If you are unsure  
whether this privacy policy is in conflict with the rules applicable where  
you are located, you should not submit your personal information to  
MathGameTime.com. IN ADDITION, IF YOU ARE LOCATED WITHIN THE EUROPEAN UNION,  
YOU SHOULD NOTE THAT YOUR INFORMATION WILL BE TRANSFERRED TO THE UNITED  
STATES, THE LAWS OF WHICH MAY BE DEEMED BY THE EUROPEAN UNION TO HAVE  
INADEQUATE DATA PROTECTION. Users of MathGameTime.com located in countries  
outside of the United States who submit personal information do thereby  
consent to the transfer of that information to and/or storage of the  
information in the United States. Cooperation with law enforcement; fraud  
protection Fila LLC fully cooperates with law enforcement agencies in  
identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve  
the right to disclose information about members who we believe are in  
violation of applicable laws or regulations, or as required to respond to a  
subpoena, court orders or other legal process requiring such disclosure. We  
also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities  
that we reasonably believe to be unlawful and to exchange information with  
other companies and organizations for fraud protection. Changes to our  
Privacy Policy Use of information we collect is subject to the Privacy  
Policy in effect at the time such information is used or collected. From  
time to time, we may change our Privacy Policy and will notify you of those  
changes by email or post a notice on MathGameTime.com. Users are bound by  
any changes to the Privacy Policy when they use MathGameTime.com after such  
changes have been first posted. Please note that if you opt out of receiving  
legal notices from us, those legal notices will still govern your use of  
MathGameTime.com, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices  
for changes. Any questions regarding our Privacy Policy should be directed  
to [support@mathgametime.com](mailto:support@mathgametime.com)
